the truck manufacturer Scania that their
green conversion was hampered by the lack of
delivery from northvold following year
the car manufacturer BMW terminated an agreement with
northvold worth two billion dollars
northvol eh right now Yes but the company
notf is threatened to its existence They have
got themselves a deadline now that they have
made this application for reconstruction
in the United States under the American Bankruptcy Code
and dangerous electrochemical product can
not pushed forward in record time just because
that the project is showered with capital
and
normal company had gained access to so